Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم الإدارة، شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
[The Glory of Queen]
[مجد الملكة]
[Episode 8]
[الحلقة 8]
In the fragrance identification round,
في جولة تحديد العطور،
Contestants Four and Six got four scents wrong,
أخطأ المتسابقان الرابع والسادس في تحديد أربع روائح.
Contestants Two and Three got two wrong,
أجاب المتسابقان الثاني والثالث إجابة خاطئة في سؤالين.
while Contestants One
بينما المتسابق الأول
and Five
وخمسة
got everything right, making them the winners of this round.
لقد أحسنوا التصرف في كل شيء، مما جعلهم الفائزين في هذه الجولة.
Those brought in at the last minute really aren't up to the task.
أولئك الذين تم جلبهم في اللحظة الأخيرة ليسوا على قدر المسؤولية.
They can't even make it into the top three.
لا يستطيعون حتى الوصول إلى المراكز الثلاثة الأولى.
In the fragrance detection round,
في جولة الكشف عن العطور،
she tied for first place with Contestant Three,
تعادلت في المركز الأول مع المتسابقة الثالثة،
and she also ranks first in fragrance identification.
وهي تحتل المرتبة الأولى أيضاً في تحديد العطور.
In such a short time, she has learned remarkably fast.
لقد تعلمت بسرعة ملحوظة في مثل هذه الفترة القصيرة .
Her talent
موهبتها
rivals that of Jingheng.
ينافس ما يقدمه جينغهينغ.
Even though Second Young Master was punished,
على الرغم من معاقبة السيد الشاب الثاني ،
he's still been concerned about your health.
لا يزال قلقاً على صحتك.
I know Jingheng is dutiful,
أعلم أن جينغهينغ شخص مطيع،
and his life hasn't been easy over the years.
ولم تكن حياته سهلة على مر السنين.
Yet the one who should have stepped up hasn't,
لكن الشخص الذي كان ينبغي عليه أن يبادر لم يفعل ذلك.
and amid all this strife,
وفي خضم كل هذا الصراع،
it seems they've forgotten that we are family.
يبدو أنهم نسوا أننا عائلة.
Madam Zhang,
السيدة تشانغ،
what do you think of that child?
ما رأيك في ذلك الطفل؟
When it comes to fragrance-making,
فيما يتعلق بصناعة العطور،
she's actually quite good.
إنها جيدة جداً في الواقع.
She's willing to focus and learn.
إنها مستعدة للتركيز والتعلم.
I've met her a few times,
لقد قابلتها عدة مرات،
and she seems sensible with her words and actions.
ويبدو أنها عاقلة في أقوالها وأفعالها.
This is the final round of the Fragrance Competition,
هذه هي الجولة النهائية من مسابقة العطور،
and it's the most important one: fragrance-making.
وهو الأهم: صناعة العطور.
Whoever comes out on top in this round
من سيفوز في هذه الجولة
will be the winner of this year's competition.
سيكون الفائز في مسابقة هذا العام.
Each of you has been provided with
تم تزويد كل واحد منكم بـ
identical fragrance-making tools,
أدوات متطابقة لصنع العطور،
so think carefully about the blend you wish to create.
لذا فكر جيداً في المزيج الذي ترغب في ابتكاره.
You have the time it takes one incense stick to burn.
لديك الوقت الكافي لاحتراق عود بخور واحد.
Now, start.
والآن، ابدأ.
You want to use the Fragrance Competition
تريد استخدام مسابقة العطور
to plant someone in the Pei family.
لزرع شخص ما في عائلة باي.
You're utterly delusional.
أنت تعيش في وهم تام.
This time,
هذه المرة،
I'll make sure you never get back on your feet.
سأضمن ألا تنهض من جديد.
The counterweight is wrong.
الثقل الموازن خاطئ.
Why has she stopped?
لماذا توقفت؟
Is there something wrong with the tool?
هل هناك مشكلة في الأداة؟
Why has Song Zhiyao stopped?
لماذا توقف سونغ تشياو؟
Looks like there's something wrong with the counterweight.
يبدو أن هناك مشكلة ما في الثقل الموازن.
If the counterweight is faulty,
إذا كان الثقل الموازن معيباً،
how can she weigh the fragrance powder?
كيف يمكنها وزن مسحوق العطر؟
Anyone can follow a recipe
بإمكان أي شخص اتباع وصفة طعام
if all the ingredients are prepared
إذا تم تحضير جميع المكونات
in the right proportions for them.
بالنسب المناسبة لهم.
But the art of crafting a fragrance lies in adaptability.
لكن فن صناعة العطور يكمن في القدرة على التكيف.
Let's just wait and see.
لننتظر ونرى.
Only if she can overcome that
فقط إذا استطاعت التغلب على ذلك
will she be the person I'm truly looking for.
هل ستكون هي الشخص الذي أبحث عنه حقاً؟
Why has Contestant Five stopped?
لماذا توقف المتسابق الخامس؟
She performed very well during the fragrance identification
لقد قدمت أداءً جيداً للغاية خلال عملية تحديد العطور
and detection rounds.
وجولات الكشف.
Fragrance identification and detection are just the basics.
إن تحديد العطور والكشف عنها ليس سوى الأساسيات.
Having a good memory or learning quickly
امتلاك ذاكرة جيدة أو التعلم بسرعة
can make someone stand out.
يمكن أن يجعل الشخص مميزاً.
But making a fragrance is different.
لكن صناعة العطور أمر مختلف.
She's only been learning for a few months.
لم تكن تتعلم إلا لبضعة أشهر.
She's likely just barely managing.
من المرجح أنها بالكاد تستطيع تدبير أمورها.
The counterweight can't be used.
لا يمكن استخدام الثقل الموازن.
Even a one-gram error can alter the scent.
حتى خطأ بمقدار غرام واحد يمكن أن يغير الرائحة.
What should I do?
ماذا علي أن أفعل؟
Is this stumping you?
هل هذا الأمر محير بالنسبة لك؟
Who do you think you're looking down on?
من تظن نفسك تنظر إليه بازدراء؟
Think a little harder.
فكر ملياً.
What was that for?
ما الغرض من ذلك؟
I didn't do anything wrong.
لم أفعل أي شيء خاطئ.
There's nothing wrong with having everything prepared in advance.
لا حرج في تجهيز كل شيء مسبقاً.
But if a situation arises,
لكن إذا نشأ موقف ما،
like not having a steelyard, or if it's broken,
مثل عدم وجود ميزان حديدي، أو إذا كان مكسوراً،
how would you make a fragrance then?
كيف يمكنك صنع عطر إذن؟
I'd just use my hands.
سأستخدم يدي فقط.
With your level of skill,
بمستوى مهارتك،
you actually dare to weigh it by hand?
هل تجرؤ حقاً على وزنها باليد؟
Besides, something this light can't possibly
إضافة إلى ذلك، هناك شيء لا يمكن لهذا الضوء أن يفعله بأي حال من الأحوال.
be measured accurately that way.
يتم قياسها بدقة بهذه الطريقة.
Then what else can I use?
إذن، ما الذي يمكنني استخدامه أيضاً؟
Use whatever you have at hand.
استخدم أي شيء متوفر لديك.
You need to know the weight of what you're carrying.
يجب أن تعرف وزن ما تحمله.
The steelyard and counterweight follow a one-hundred-to-one ratio.
تتبع العارضة الفولاذية والثقل الموازن نسبة مائة إلى واحد.
In other words,
بعبارة أخرى،
your old counterweight could measure objects up to ten liang at most.
كان بإمكان ثقل الموازنة القديم الخاص بك قياس أشياء يصل حجمها إلى عشرة ليانغ كحد أقصى.
Once you understand this principle,
بمجرد أن تفهم هذا المبدأ،
even a branch can serve as a steelyard.
حتى الغصن يمكن أن يكون بمثابة حبل فولاذي.
So,
لذا،
I can use this as well?
هل يمكنني استخدام هذا أيضاً؟
Absolutely.
قطعاً.
♪We first met♪
♪التقينا لأول مرة♪
♪The wind blew softly♪
هبت الرياح برفق
♪Our eyes met♪
♪تلاقت أعيننا♪
♪And the heart was stirred♪
♪ وتحرك القلب ♪
♪That tender affection♪
♪ذلك الحنان الرقيق♪
♪Shone through the eyes♪
♪تألقت من خلال العيون♪
♪Your smile captured my heart♪
ابتسامتك أسرت قلبي
♪Night and day, we stay close♪
♪ليلاً ونهاراً، نبقى قريبين♪
♪Dreaming together quietly♪
♪نحلم معًا بهدوء♪
♪The scent of sweetness♪
♪رائحة الحلاوة♪
♪Floats high in the clouds♪
♪تحلق عالياً في السحاب♪
♪We are in sync with each other♪
♪نحن متناغمون مع بعضنا البعض♪
♪Secretly caring for you♪
♪أهتم بك سراً♪
♪You alone hold my heart♪
♪أنتِ وحدكِ تملكين قلبي♪
♪I don't know when we started♪
♪لا أعرف متى بدأنا♪
It's ready.
إنه جاهز.
♪Making memories together♪
♪نصنع الذكريات معاً♪
♪I only wish your feelings mirror mine♪
أتمنى فقط أن تعكس مشاعرك مشاعري
♪I'll never betray this love♪
لن أخون هذا الحب أبداً
I think Contestant One's fragrance stands out the most.
أعتقد أن عطر المتسابق الأول هو الأبرز.
How about you all?
ماذا عنكم جميعاً؟
Yes,
نعم،
I also quite like Contestant One's fragrance powder.
كما أنني معجبة جداً بمسحوق العطر الخاص بالمتسابقة الأولى.
I actually think Contestant Five's fragrance powder
أعتقد في الواقع أن بودرة عطر المتسابقة الخامسة
is exceptionally unique.
فريد من نوعه بشكل استثنائي.
It's named "Sober Intoxication."
اسمها "السكر الرصين".
The cleverest touch is the addition of rice liquor,
أما اللمسة الأكثر ذكاءً فهي إضافة مشروب الأرز الكحولي.
creating a feeling of being on the verge of intoxication.
مما يخلق شعوراً بالوقوع على حافة السكر.
To accomplish this in just the time it takes
لإنجاز ذلك في الوقت الذي يستغرقه الأمر فقط
for one incense stick to burn
لإشعال عود بخور واحد
(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
(شاهد على www.dramacool.club دعم الإدارة)
is no small feat.
ليس هذا بالأمر الهين.
What do you all think?
ما رأيكم جميعاً؟
I think Contestant Five's fragrance is the most unique.
أعتقد أن عطر المتسابق الخامس هو الأكثر تميزاً.
We also choose Contestant Five.
نختار أيضاً المتسابق رقم خمسة.
The winner of this year's Fragrance Competition
الفائز في مسابقة العطور لهذا العام
is Contestant Five,
هو المتسابق رقم خمسة،
Song Zhiyao.
سونغ تشياو.
I knew it would be her.
كنت أعرف أنها ستكون هي.
I told you she could make it.
قلت لك إنها تستطيع فعلها.
Go
يذهب
and bring her over.
وأحضرها معك.
Yes.
نعم.
Thank you, My Lady.
شكراً لكِ يا سيدتي.
Don't assume that being the winner
لا تفترض أن كونك الفائز
makes you special.
يجعلك مميزاً.
You got lucky this time,
لقد حالفك الحظ هذه المرة،
but the Pei family values real skill above all.
لكن عائلة باي تُقدّر المهارة الحقيقية فوق كل شيء.
You're right, My Lady.
أنتِ محقة يا سيدتي.
Starting today,
ابتداءً من اليوم،
I will not slack off.
لن أتهاون.
I'll devote myself to studying fragrance-making.
سأكرس نفسي لدراسة صناعة العطور.
Miss Song,
الآنسة سونغ،
Madam would like to see you.
تود السيدة رؤيتك.
Greetings, Madam.
تحية طيبة سيدتي.
Take a seat.
تفضل بالجلوس.
No need. I can just stand here.
لا داعي لذلك. يمكنني فقط الوقوف هنا.
Who else is in your family?
من هم أفراد عائلتك الآخرون؟
I… I've been an orphan since I was little.
أنا... لقد كنت يتيماً منذ صغري.
I was taken in by an old beggar,
استقبلني متسول عجوز،
but he passed away a few years ago.
لكنه توفي قبل بضع سنوات.
Good girl.
فتاة جيدة.
Who taught you how to read and write?
من علمك القراءة والكتابة؟
The old beggar who took me in
المتسول العجوز الذي آواني
was once a scholar.
كان في يوم من الأيام عالماً.
He ended up in misfortune after breaking his leg in an accident.
انتهى به الأمر في محنة بعد أن كسر ساقه في حادث.
He taught many kids how to read and write.
لقد علّم العديد من الأطفال القراءة والكتابة.
It's fate that Jingheng brought you
من تدبير القدر أن جلبك جينغهينغ
to the Pei Manor.
إلى قصر باي.
Be honest with me,
كن صادقاً معي،
do you wish to learn more?
هل ترغب في معرفة المزيد؟
Staying at the Pei Manor
الإقامة في قصر باي
is the only way to get more clues to find my aunt.
إنها الطريقة الوحيدة للحصول على المزيد من الأدلة للعثور على عمتي.
Of course, I do.
بالطبع، أفعل.
Then would you be willing to marry into the Pei Manor?
هل ستكونين مستعدة للزواج من عائلة بي مانور؟
I have two grandsons.
لدي حفيدان.
You may marry whichever one you prefer.
يمكنك الزواج من أي شخص تفضله.
Marry...?
الزواج...؟
♪The secret about you is buried deep in my heart♪
♪سرّك مدفونٌ في أعماق قلبي♪
♪I draw near, then pull away, fearing I might yield to this attraction♪
♪أقترب، ثم أبتعد، خوفاً من أن أستسلم لهذا الانجذاب♪
♪I like to think I'm keeping my cool♪
أحب أن أعتقد أنني أحافظ على هدوئي.
♪But my instincts keep pulling me closer♪
لكن غرائزي تستمر في جذبي إلى أقرب نقطة
♪Unwittingly, I've fallen completely for you♪
♪دون أن أدري، وقعت في حبك تماماً♪
♪Can the sacrifices of this life measure the depth of love?♪
هل يمكن لتضحيات هذه الحياة أن تقيس عمق الحب؟
♪It's too late to summon the courage to hold you once more♪
♪لقد فات الأوان لاستجماع الشجاعة لاحتضانك مرة أخرى♪
♪Having witnessed all the world's splendor♪
♪بعد أن شهدنا كل روعة العالم♪
♪I've felt joy and sorrow for one soul alone♪
♪شعرت بالفرح والحزن من أجل روح واحدة فقط♪
♪For our kindred souls, all I can give is this humble heart♪
♪لأرواحنا المتآلفة، كل ما أستطيع تقديمه هو هذا القلب المتواضع♪
♪If I encounter you in this life♪
♪إذا صادفتك في هذه الحياة♪
♪Fate is already fulfilled♪
♪لقد تحقق القدر بالفعل♪
♪Let this chapter become a memory, breaking free from destiny♪
♪دع هذا الفصل يصبح ذكرى، متحرراً من قيود القدر♪
♪In the next life, may the course of time lead me to you♪
♪في الحياة الأخرى، أتمنى أن يقودني الزمن إليك♪
♪With a sincere heart, I shall carry our love forward♪
♪بقلبٍ صادق، سأحمل حبنا إلى الأمام♪